A Guide to the Grayson County (Va.) Board of Supervisors Records, 1891-1972 (bulk 1965-1972)
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Grayson County (Va.) Board of Supervisors Records, 1891-1972 (bulk 1965-1972)
The Library of Virginia
1047193-1047200, 1128748, 0007727532
10 boxes.
Grayson County (Va.) Circuit Court.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
These items came to the Library of Virginia in a shipment of court papers from Grayson County.
Historical Information
Grayson County was named for William Grayson, a delegate to the Continental Congress from 1784 to 1787 and one of the first two United States senators from Virginia. It was formed from Wythe County in 1792, and a part of Patrick County was added in 1810.
Scope and Content
Grayson County (Va.) Board of Supervisors Records, 1891-1972 (bulk 1965-1972) contains Minutes consisting of papers and correspondence for the years 1965-1972. This collection also includes a record of Witnesses Before the Board of Supervisors (1905), Road Books (1891, 1902-1903), highway and road papers (1931-1945), and papers and correspondences related to the Catawba Sanatorium (1936-1938), Southwestern State Hospital (1936-1937), Virginia Emergency Relief Administration (1934-1936), and Virginia Home for Incurables (1936).
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Related Material
Additional Grayson County Court Records can be found on microfilm at the Library of Virginia. Consult "A Guide to Virginia County and City Records on Microfilm"
Index Terms
Corporate Names:
Grayson County (Va.) Circuit Court
Subjects:
Public Records--Virginia--Grayson County
Geographical Names:
Grayson County (Va.)--History
Genre and Form Terms:
Local government Records--Virginia--Grayson County
Contents List
- Road Book and Witnesses Before Board of Supervisors, 1891-1905 (bulk 1902-1903)
  The Road Book includes records for 1891 and 1902-1903. The Witnesses Before Board of Supervisors includes records for 1905.
- Papers and Correspondence, 1931-1945, 1963-1968
  These records are correspondences, papers, agendas, and meeting minutes that relate to budgets, ordinances, Catawba Sanatorium (1936-1938), highways and roads (1931-1945), Southwestern State Hospital (1936-1937), Virginia Emergency Relief Administration (1934-1936), and Virginia Home for Incurables (1936).
- Minutes (Papers and Correspondence), 1965-1966
  These records are minutes which consists of papers and correspondence.
- Minutes (Papers and Correspondence), 1967-1968
- Minutes (Papers and Correspondence), 1968
- Minutes (Papers and Correspondence), 1969
- Minutes (Papers and Correspondence), 1969-1970
- Minutes (Papers and Correspondence), 1970-1971
- Minutes (Papers and Correspondence), 1971
- Minutes (Papers and Correspondence), 1972